<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cycling on bonoms.net</title>
    <link>https://bonoms.net/tags/cycling/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cycling on bonoms.net</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Lorenzo Bonomi</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 10:54:08 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://bonoms.net/tags/cycling/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to analyze cycling power data with intervals.icu</title>
      <link>https://bonoms.net/posts/powerdata/powerdata/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 10:54:08 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bonoms.net/posts/powerdata/powerdata/</guid>
      <description>If you want to analyze your power data there&amp;rsquo;s a free online tool called intervals.icu, it is community based, open suorce and allows you to do amazing stuff. I made a quick video about it, sorry if quality is not the best. Some people told me music is too loud, i agree!!! But i&amp;rsquo;m too lazy to upload it again&amp;hellip; :)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Absolute Black CRAP oval chainring</title>
      <link>https://bonoms.net/posts/crap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 10:54:08 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bonoms.net/posts/crap/</guid>
      <description>Got some issues with absolute black oval chainring: shifting after not many km is impossible. Also issues with powermeter displaying too many watts :( i&amp;rsquo;m gonna give a physical explaination soon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to fuel in cycling, myth BUSTED!</title>
      <link>https://bonoms.net/posts/carbs-intake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 10:54:08 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bonoms.net/posts/carbs-intake/</guid>
      <description>Hey, let&amp;rsquo;s talk about cycling nutrition, a topic often misunderstood. While I&amp;rsquo;m not a nutritionist, I&amp;rsquo;ve observed some common misconceptions. For instance, every cycling daddy I know in the week-end goes put for 150k rides without eating&amp;hellip;&#xA;Carb the fuck up You might think that during low-intensity rides (regular pace for a &amp;gt;100k ride), your body primarily burns fat for fuel. While there&amp;rsquo;s truth to this, recent evidence suggests that even at low intensities, carbohydrates play a significant role in fueling your ride.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
