<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>bonoms.net</title>
    <link>https://bonoms.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on bonoms.net</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Lorenzo Bonomi</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 10:13:40 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://bonoms.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Where to Hitch a Sling on an Axle in Crevasse Rescue - Overkill Analysis</title>
      <link>https://bonoms.net/posts/puntopicca/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 10:13:40 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bonoms.net/posts/puntopicca/</guid>
      <description>While I was on a glacier yesterday, we were practicing some crevasse rescue operations. The glacier was covered in deep snow. The most common thing to do when a person falls into a crevasse is to firstly secure the person with a glacier sling attached to an axle placed vertically. Then you have to make two fixed points to recover the person with a hoist.&#xA;In the case of a glacier exposed with ice, you can simply use ice screws, but in the case of yesterday&amp;rsquo;s scenario, it is common to dig an axle with a sling coming out and build an anchor from it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alpinismo - Cima Presanella</title>
      <link>https://bonoms.net/mountain/presanella/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 10:54:08 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bonoms.net/mountain/presanella/</guid>
      <description>Descrizione Una scammellata di 12 ore, ottimo per chi non ha mai provato l&amp;rsquo;ambiente alta montagna e vuole avvicinarsi all&amp;rsquo;utilizzo di picca e ramponi (ovviamente necessari per questo itinerario). Difatti questa è stata la mia prima esperienza in alta quota, non scrivo altro perchè non ero molto attento ai passaggi e scrivo a distanza di mesi quindi questa non va assolutamente considerata come relazione, si possono però apprezzare le foto :)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skimo - Anticima Gavia &#43; Passo Nord Zebrù</title>
      <link>https://bonoms.net/mountain/forni/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 10:54:08 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bonoms.net/mountain/forni/</guid>
      <description>Descrizione Belissima gita sulla strada innevata del passo gavia, il pendio è inizialmente molto dolve e si sviluppa bene. Ambiente top. Dopo aver dormito in rifugio il secondo giorno abbiamo girato per il passo zebrù trovando tuttavia neve molto ventata, abbiamo girato i tacchi e siamo andati a berci la birra.&#xA;Traccia anticima Gavia Traccia passo nord Zebrù Foto </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SkiMo - Monte della Neve</title>
      <link>https://bonoms.net/mountain/montedellaneve/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 10:54:08 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bonoms.net/mountain/montedellaneve/</guid>
      <description>Descrizione Una classica nelle zone livignasche. Partenza a &amp;ldquo;motore freddo&amp;rdquo; perché c&amp;rsquo;erano molti gradi sotto zero. Siamo poi scesi dalla pista in quanto le condizioni non erano ottimali.&#xA;Traccia Foto </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to analyze cycling power data with intervals.icu</title>
      <link>https://bonoms.net/posts/powerdata/powerdata/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 10:54:08 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bonoms.net/posts/powerdata/powerdata/</guid>
      <description>If you want to analyze your power data there&amp;rsquo;s a free online tool called intervals.icu, it is community based, open suorce and allows you to do amazing stuff. I made a quick video about it, sorry if quality is not the best. Some people told me music is too loud, i agree!!! But i&amp;rsquo;m too lazy to upload it again&amp;hellip; :)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Absolute Black CRAP oval chainring</title>
      <link>https://bonoms.net/posts/crap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 10:54:08 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bonoms.net/posts/crap/</guid>
      <description>Got some issues with absolute black oval chainring: shifting after not many km is impossible. Also issues with powermeter displaying too many watts :( i&amp;rsquo;m gonna give a physical explaination soon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to fuel in cycling, myth BUSTED!</title>
      <link>https://bonoms.net/posts/carbs-intake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 10:54:08 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bonoms.net/posts/carbs-intake/</guid>
      <description>Hey, let&amp;rsquo;s talk about cycling nutrition, a topic often misunderstood. While I&amp;rsquo;m not a nutritionist, I&amp;rsquo;ve observed some common misconceptions. For instance, every cycling daddy I know in the week-end goes put for 150k rides without eating&amp;hellip;&#xA;Carb the fuck up You might think that during low-intensity rides (regular pace for a &amp;gt;100k ride), your body primarily burns fat for fuel. While there&amp;rsquo;s truth to this, recent evidence suggests that even at low intensities, carbohydrates play a significant role in fueling your ride.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who is bonoms?</title>
      <link>https://bonoms.net/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 10:54:08 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bonoms.net/about/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my website! If you&amp;rsquo;re curious about who I am, u&amp;rsquo;re in the right spot.&#xA;Yes, I&amp;rsquo;ve changed a bit since then, but that&amp;rsquo;s life (fucking good song of FS). Currently, I&amp;rsquo;m studying Physical Engineering at Politecnico di Milano, but my home base is in Valtellina, a valley in the Italian Alps. Stick around!!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
